It has begun. Nighttime and Idol Dialogue Series
Yes, this is Nakamiyamako. This is Nakayamashiko, attendance number 12.
And,
I'm Riko Ueda from XXXXXXXXXXXX.
Pleased to meet you.
Riko Riko.
That's great.
We don't get a chance to talk much even when we perform together at live concerts.
Hey. That's right.
So, aren't you a little nervous?
A little nervous. And it's just the two of us.
We're the same age,
No honorifics.
I'm talking to someone your age.
I get it.
I get it. I get it.
That's great.
But we're still on.
Hey.
First of all, we have a name.
We have the same name.
Same age.
Born in the fall.
November?
Surely it's October.
So we are close.
And we have the same blood type.
O.
O-ish?
B-ish?
B or AB?
Yes, I am a little AB-ish.
O-ish?
I didn't think I was O-ish.
I didn't think so.
But, Riko.
But I guess it makes sense now that you say I'm O-ish.
You are very O-ish.
Is that what people say?
I have a rough impression of you.
What should I call you?
I'm still stuck with honorifics.
Right now I call her Riko-chan,
So I'm Riko-chan, too.
I don't know what to call her, and I can't express it in kanji.
Kanji is different, so I can't express it yet.
But when I call you Riko, it's the same.
I've usually been called Tatehata.
Do you have any nicknames by which you have been called?
I've always been called Tachibata.
Ever since I was very young.
When I was little, I was Rashiko-chan,
I've been Tachibata since I was in Mebi Junior High School or junior high school.
On the other hand, when I was little, I was called Rachan,
Rashi-chan.
Then it changed to Riko-chan or Riko.
What is your nickname now?
Almost always Rashiko-chan.
Also, I'm often called by my first name.
Ueda.
Ueda-heart?
No way.
Fans often call me Ueda-san, too.
I like it. I like Nashi-chan.
And Tachibata.
I still know that too.
Is that okay?
Tatehata.
I'll go with that.
That's settled.
And you have a dog.
Yes, I do.
Marupu.
Me too, Poo-Poo.
Poo-poo.
We have something in common.
Puppies.
Still young?
He turned 1 year old.
Still one year old?
Instagram.
Post a lot.
How old are you?
I'm 14.
I'm a senior.
You're a grandmother now.
You're becoming one.
Still going strong.
It's soothing, isn't it?It's soothing, isn't it?
It's soothing.
Have you been together since you were little?
Yes. I've had him since he was a child.
Why did you decide to buy it?
I don't know.
I used to be against it, but I thought it would be too much work for a dog.
Last year, I went to a bed store,
I said I liked her, and there was an opportunity for me to live with her for a night or two,
When I took him home, he said he would buy it.
My parents agreed.
He would be so cute at home.
It would be so comforting.
When I came home from work, he was a toy.
It's cute.
What's a wook?
That's right. Wook.
What's your name?
Ran-chan.
Ah! Lan-chan.
But it's like a French dog, like a toyoodle is a French dog.
Is that so?
I didn't know that.
I had no idea.
So, I just went with "Lan," which is French for there.
Fran, I see.
A dog.
Where did that come from?
His name is Uku, and he was a little baby when he came to us,
In Hawaiian, small is uk.
Oh, wow.
But now he's big. It's amazing.
He's grown up.
Big but uk.
Yeah, yeah.
What else do we have in common?
What else do we have in common? I don't know.
The fact that he's buying Fran and..,
Science fiction?
Hmm?
What do you do?
Usually?
I go shopping a lot.
I like clothes and stuff, so I go look at different places.
I try to sleep.
I'm usually just hanging out at home.
But I'm also hanging around.
Sleeping all the time? Or do they wake up early and just hang around?
There's also something else.
Which is it?
When I can sleep, I sleep all the time, but it's just too lazy,
I do set an alarm, though,
But I don't realize that I set the alarm and then stop it, so I wake up about 2 hours later.
Ahh...
Can you get up? Soon.
I'm a strong morning person,
But when I'm not working, I sleep. I lie in bed all day.
Do you do anything at home?
Yes.
I do nothing when I have nothing to do at home.
I also go to comedy clubs.
Who is your favorite comedy idol?
I like Wagyu the most.
For now, I just go.
Do you go to live shows?
It's fun, isn't it?
Have you ever been?
Maybe once? But it was a lot of fun.
I'll go sometime.
I want to go! I want you to take me there.
Let's go. I'll introduce you.
There's Shinjuku, Shibuya.
There's also Fukuoka.
I want to go!
Let's go. Let's do this.
But on the other hand, I'm looking forward to shopping for clothes and stuff.
I'm looking forward to shopping.
What kind of clothes do you like?
I usually wear very casual clothes,
But I also have a garish image of Bittan,
I love to look at them.
But I don't have the courage to wear it myself.
I want you to wear it. Today's outfit is really cute.
Scout.
I've had them wear it, so I'll let them pick it out for me.
I want to go!
I haven't had a chance to talk to you even if I see you at a concert or something.
You're not shy at all, are you?
I'm not shy, but I do get nervous.
Shy?
I can't talk.I can't talk.
Isn't that what nervousness is?
But so is batten.
What? No way.
You don't think so?
I think I'm close.
He's quiet.
He never leaves school.
Yeah, that's true.
That's true. That's why there are events like StarPlaza Fest,
Riko-chan, even if I wanted to take your picture..,
She's not there.
I often feel that she is not there.
I'm glad. Today.
We talked about this before at the rehearsal for the Stapler Fest,
That's really about it.
Even at the first Staplerfest,
We ran into each other,
We took a picture and said goodbye.
That's true. I take pictures only with Rikuchan. At StarPlaza.
Really?
That's right. I don't take many pictures at all.
I see. But I'm a senior too.
That's right.
I don't take pictures.
That's great.
What do we have in common?
What color do you like?
What color? What color?
But I usually go for red.
I like red.
I see.
But lately I've been wearing a lot of blue.
But it looks good on you.
You look great in red.
I love red.
I love red and blue,
Tied.
The primary color is blue.
But I usually think of it as pastel or white.
You think it doesn't suit you?
But red in general?
Is it true that I don't wear red too often?
But your lesson shoes are bright red.
That's how it happened.
It's about time I wore red shoes.
I'm taking them out.
I don't usually wear bright red.
Unless I'm wearing a costume.
That's right.
Red looks great on you.
The light blue looks great on you.
Thank you very much.
We both feel like a group.
I'm probably going to join Rikitan,
Atfly Live, huh?
Yes, I remember. I remember that.
I went to see Atfly Live for the first time,
Even after that, Megumi Eguchi was always so cool,
Her dancing and singing are so powerful,
We often talk about how we want to do this kind of live show based on Megumi Eguchi's live performance.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your time.
It seems that many groups are performing at StarPlaza,
They have a unique view of the world,
The songs have a very impressive worldview,
Everyone was dancing together backstage.
I was so happy.
Everyone is glued to the stage.
That's not the case at all.
We played the same song all the time at the STAPLA festival,
It was so much fun.
Everyone was watching backstage.
It made me happy.
It was fun.
I'm still thinking that I was too aggressive.
We all want to see you live when it's Eguchi-chan,
We were together at Setouchi Ai the other night, weren't we?
We were together, weren't we?
I was watching the whole time.
We were all dancing together in the backyard.
We were dancing together.
It was like that.
It was the end of the first half,
Approaching the time,
Tomorrow is the last half of the game,
Let's talk a lot more.
Yes, I will. We will talk.